A Finding Aid to the Lucy R. Lippard Papers, 1930s-2007, bulk 1960s-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.lipplucy
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1950s-2006; Series 2; 28.8 Linear feet Boxes 1-28, 51, OVs 54-63
  - Correspondence by Name, 1950s-2006; 2.1
    - Berge, Carol, circa 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Berge, Carol, circa 1980-1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Berkeley Art Project, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Berkley, Sheila, circa 1976-1987 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Bernheim, Stephanie, circa 1977-circa 1982 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Bernstein, Judith, 1977-1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Berry, Gene, circa 1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Beuys, Joseph, circa 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 1 and OV 60
    - Bien, Ania, circa 1979-circa 1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Bienal del Grabado Latinoamericano, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Binns, Vivienne, circa 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Binns, Vivienne, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Binns, Vivienne, 1982-1991 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Blevino, J. R., circa 1973 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Blocher, Heidi, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Bloom, Miriam, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Bloom, Suzanne, circa 1970s-1991 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Blumenthal, Lyn, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - BobsBand, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Bochner, Mel, circa 1969-circa 1973 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Boetti, Anne-Marie, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Bornstein, Gloria, circa 1977-1993 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Bornstein, Gloria, "Public Document", 1977 May 30; 1 Sound cassettes Cassette is copy of original recording. Location of original is unknown. (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan, circa 1969-circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Borstein, Elena, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Boston Visual Artists Union Incorporated, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Bourgeois, Louise, circa 1969-1990 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Bowen, Jerry, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Boyce, Janet, circa 1978-1987 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Braderman, Joan, circa 1970s-1984 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Brandeis University, Rose Art Museum, 1966; 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC), 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Bromm, Hal (Hal Bromm Gallery), circa 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Broner, Esther (E. M.) and Robert, 1970s-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bronx Museum of the Arts, 1979, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Broodthaers, Marcel, circa 1968-circa 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Carol, 1981-1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Francis (Frank), 1970s-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Includes 5 "splatter-dash" paintings on postcards
    - Brouwn, Stanley, 1960s-1970s (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Buchanan, Beverly, 1970s-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Includes photos of Buchanan
    - Buchanan, Nancy, circa 1980s (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Buffalo State College, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Burckhardt, Rudolph, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Oversized material housed in OV 55
    - Burgin, Victor, 1960s-1970s (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Burgy, Donald, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Burton, Dennis, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Butterfield, Jan, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Button, John, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Byars, James Lee, circa 1969-circa 1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Oversized material housed in OV 60
    - B, General: B.-Bai, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - B, General: Bak-Ban, 1960s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - B, General: Bar-Bay, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - B, General: Bea-Ben, 1970s-2002 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - B, General: Ber-Bev, 1960s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - B, General: Bi-Bj, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - B, General: Bl, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - B, General: Bo, 1960s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - B, General: Bra-Bri, 1960s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - B, General: Bro-Bry, 1970s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - B, General: Bu, 1960s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 2
    - B, General: By, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - B, First Names Only, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - B, Illegible, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Caccaro, Carey, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Cagan, Steve, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 32-34)
    - Caglioti, Victor, circa 1968-circa 1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Cajori, Marion, 1980s-1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Calender, Arden, 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - California Institute of the Arts, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Carson, Neke, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Caruthers-Aiken, Maryanne, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Caruthers-Aiken, Maryanne, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Caruthers-Aiken, Maryanne, NPR Options Broadcast, circa 1980s; 1 Sound cassettes Labels read: Side 1, "Land As Symbol" Peter Navakoff. Side 2, N. Scot Monoday. (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Castle, Frederick, circa 1968-circa 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - Cavellini, Guglielmo Achille, circa 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Celant, Germano, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Celender, Don, circa 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Celender, Don, 1971-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Center for Constitutional Rights, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Center for Ecology and Social Justice, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Centre Georges Pompidou, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Chicago, Judy, circa 1971-1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Chin, Daryl, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Christo and Jean-Claude, 1960s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Chrysalis, circa 1977-circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Ciobataru, Gillian Wise, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Claire Copley Gallery Inc., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Clarke, Richard and Masters, Deborah, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Cohen, Mirit, circa 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Colby College Museum of Art, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Colette, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - College Art Association, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Collins, James, circa 1960s-1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Committee for the Visual Arts, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Community Artists Cultural Survey Committee, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Cone, Fred Cornell, circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Oversized material housed in Box 51 Folder 4
    - Connell, Clyde, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Contemporary Arts Museum, Houston, Texas, 1970s, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Conwill, Houston, circa 1970s-1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Cook, Christopher C., 1970s (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
    - Cook, Christopher C., 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Copp, Fletcher, 1974-1977, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Cornell University, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Cotton, Paul, 1960s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Cowden, Brian, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Includes photo of Cowden
    - Crickmay, Chris, 1970s-1988 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Criteria, circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Culbertson, Janet, 1970s-1992 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Curman, Billy, circa 1977 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Curnoe, Greg, "Recorded Letter to Lucy Lippard", 1969 February 26; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Cutforth, Roger, circa 1971-circa 1972 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - C, General: C.-Cal, 1960s-1980s (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - C, General: Cam-Cay, 1960s-1980s (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - C, General: Ce, 1970s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - C, General: Ch, 1960s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - C, General: Ci-Cl, 1960s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - C, General: Coc-Col, 1970s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - C, General: Com-Cop, 1960s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - C, General: Cor-Cou, 1970s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - C, General: Cr-Cy, 1960s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - C, First Names Only, 1970s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Daddaland/Bay Area Daddaists, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Daddaland/Bay Area Daddaists, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Daddaland/Bay Area Daddaists, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Darboven, Hanne, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Darboven, Hanne, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Darboven, Hanne, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Darboven, Hanne, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Darboven, Hanne, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Darboven, Hanne, 1976-1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Davidovich, Jaime, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Includes photo of Davidovich
    - Davidson Carol Kreeger, circa 1973-circa 1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Aubrey, circa 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Day, Worden, 1970s-1980s (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - de Antonio, Emile, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - De Appel (Wies Smals and Aggy Smeets), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - De Bretteville, Sheila, 1974-1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - De Gogorza, Patricia, circa 1973-1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - De Mott, Helen, circa 1970-1985 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Dean, Peter, 1971-1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Denes, Agnes, circa 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Dennis, Charles, circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Dias, Antonia, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Dibbets, Jan, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Dibbets, Jan, circa 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Dikeakos, Christos, circa 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Dimitrijevic, Braco, 1971-1978 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Doner, Michele, circa 1980-1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Dordevic, Goran, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Downey, Margaret, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Downsbrough, Peter, circa 1969-1980 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Drescher, Tim, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Dubroof, Patricia, circa 1983 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Dwyer, Gary C., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - D, General: D.-Da, 1970s-2000 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - D, General: De, 1960s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - D, General: Dee-Dev, 1960s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - D, General: Di, 1960s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - D, General: Dj-Do, 1969-1980s (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - D, General: Dr-Dy, 1960s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - D, First Names Only, 1960s-1980s (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - D, Illegible, 1970s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - E. P. Dutton & Co., Inc., 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Eastern Michigan University, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Edelson, Mary Beth, circa 1972-1989 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1972-1977 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1984-1989 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Efrat, Benni, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Eisenberg, Ed, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Elder, Gene Wesley, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ely, Bonita, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Evans, Georgann, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Evans, Jan, circa 1972-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Everman, Welch, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Ewing, Lauren, circa 1979-circa 1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Exit Art, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Experiments in Art and Technology (E.A.T.), circa 1965-circa 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
    - Experiments in Art and Technology (E.A.T.), 1965-1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Export, Valie, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - E, General: E.-Em, 1970s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - E, General: En-Er, 1970s-2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - E, General: Es-Ex, 1960s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - E, First Names Only, 1970s-1980s (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Faris, James, 2000-2006 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Fashion Moda, circa 1980-circa 1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Fat City School of Fine Arts, circa 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Feckner, John/Don Leicht, 1980s; includes 45 rpm vinyl record (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Feigenbaum, Harriet, 1970s-1980s (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Feminist Writer's Guild, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Ferguson, Gerald, circa 1970-circa 1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Ferguson, Kathleen, 1970s-1980s (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Ferrer, Raphael, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Fischer, Konrad, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Fisher, Carole, 1974-1982 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Fisk, Anita K., 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Five/Cinco Aesthetics Limited, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Flanagan, Barry, circa 1962-circa 1978 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1967-1977 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Fleming, Avis, circa 1970-circa 1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Fleming, Madeline Frost, circa 1974-1983 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Florida State University, Museum of Fine Arts, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Concerns catalog essay Lippard wrote for Judy Chicago retrospective
    - Flynt, Henry, 1968-1974 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Focke, Anne (And/Or Gallery), circa 1973-1980 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Follett, Lyn, 1970s-1992 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Formanek, David, 1970s-1980s (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Fox, Geoffrey, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Franklin Furnace, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Franklin Furnace, 1979-1997 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Fredman, Faiya, 1974-1980 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Friedman, Ken, circa 1965-1972 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Friedman, Ken, circa 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Friedrich, Susi, 1970s-1993 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Frye, Hugo N., circa 1970-circa 1971 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Fulton, Hamish, 1969-1974 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Fusco, Coco, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - F, General: Fa, 1970s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - F, General: Fe, 1970s-1980s (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - F, General: Fi, 1960s-1998 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - F, General: Fl-Fo, 1970s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - F, General: Fr-Fu, 1970s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - F, First Names Only, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Gaess, Jacquie, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Gaines, Charlie, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Gallagher, Carole, 1979-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Galligan, J.A.N., 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - George and Gilbert, 1960s-1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gettysburg College, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Giii, Ron, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
    - Gilardi, Piero, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Giorno, John, circa 1970s (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Glier, Mike, circa 1976-circa 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Goldbard, Arlene, 1982-1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Golden, Eunice, 1973-1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Golub, Leon, 1960s-1989 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goodyear, John, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Gordh, Bill, circa 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Gordh, Bill, 1983-1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Graham, Dan, circa 1960s (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Graham, Dan, 1960s-1970s (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Graham, Dan, 1967-1975 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Graves, Nancy, circa 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Graves, Nancy, 1976-1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Gray, Jane K., 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Greenberg, Gloria and Martin, circa 1965-circa 1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Greenstein, Ilise, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Groh, Klaus, circa 1970-circa 1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Guerilla Art Action Group (Jon Hendricks and Jean Toche), circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Guerilla Art Action Group (Jon Hendricks and Jean Toche), 1971-1992 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Guerilla Girls, 1987-1993 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Gussow, Alan, 1966; 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - G, General: Ga, 1960s-1990s (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - G, General: Ge, 1970s-1980s (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - G, General: Gh-Gil, 1970s-1990s (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - G, General: Gin-Gl, 1970s-2000 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - G, General: Go, 1960s-1980s (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - G, General: Gr, 1960s-1990s (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - G, General: Gu, 1970s-1990s (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - G, First Names Only, 1970s-1990s (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Haacke, Hans, 1971, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Haber, Joel, circa 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Hall, Susan, 1970s-1980s (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Hammond, Harmony, circa 1977-1993 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Hamouda, Amy, circa 1978 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Hamrod, Lloyd, circa 1973-circa 1976 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Harding, David, 1980-1987 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Hardinger, Ruth, circa 1975-1991 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Harlam, Meg, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Harris, Ethelyn, circa 1977-1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Harrison, Charles, circa 1970-circa 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Harrison, Margaret, circa 1977-1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harry N. Abrams, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harry N. Abrams, Inc., Ad Reinhardt Manuscript, 1966-1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hartman, Arleen, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Harvard University Graduate School of Design, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Hatje, Verlag Gerd, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Healy, Anne, circa 1978-1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Heath, Gloria W., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Heimann, Anne, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Heiss, Alanna, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Hemenway, Audrey, circa 1970s-1984 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Hendricks, Geoff, 1967-1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Henes, Donna, 1960s-1980 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Henes, Donna, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Henes, Donna, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Henes, Donna, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
    - Henes, Donna, 1981-1989 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Hera (aka Betty Voelkner), 1970s-1989 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Hera (aka Betty Voelkner), circa 1981-circa 1984 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Hera (aka Betty Voelkner), circa 1987-circa 1989 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Heresies Collective, circa 1970s-1989 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Heresies Collective, circa 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Heresies Collective, circa 1990s; 1 Sound cassettes (microcassette) (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Hess, Elizabeth (Betsy), circa 1968-circa 1983 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Hicks, Margaret, 1976-1988 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Higgins, Dan, circa 1980-circa 1985 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Higgins, Dick, 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Higgins, E. F., 1970s (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Highwater, Jamake, 1970s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Hills, Patricia, 1989-2000 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Hitner, Charles (Chuck), 1980s (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Holt, Nancy, 1973-1992 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Holt, Virginia, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Holter Museum of Art, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Holtzmann, Harry, 1969-1982 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Holzer, Jenny, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Holzer, Jenny, 1979-1988 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Hompson, Davi Det, circa 1973 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Hoo Hoo Archives, circa 1973 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Horvitz, Robert, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Hudson Review, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Hudson River Museum, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Hui, Helene, 1970s-1985 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Hunter, Alexis, 1970s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Hunter, Alexis, 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Hunter, Alexis, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Hunter College of the City of the University of New York (Mac Wells Exhibition), 1995-1996; 1980 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Hynes, Frances, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - H, General: Haa-Hal, 1960s-1990s (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - H, General: Ham-Han, 1960s-1990s (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - H, General: Har-Hay, 1970s-1990s (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - H, General: He, 1960s-1990s (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - H, General: Hi, 1970s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - H, General: Hoc-Hol, 1960s-1970s (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - H, General: Hoo-Hy, 1970s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - H, First Names Only, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - H, Illegible, 1970s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Illinois Institute of Technology, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Image Blank/New Era Social Club, 1971-1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Images and Issues Magazine, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Independent Curators Incorporated, 1976-1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1976, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Indyke, Dottie (Doris), circa 1980s-1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Institute for Women and the Future, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Institute of Contemporary Arts, London, 1970s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Iskin, Ruth, 1975-1992 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Iwamoto, Ralph, circa 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - I, General: I.-In, 1960s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - I, General: In-Iv, 1970s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - I, First Names Only, 1960s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Jagger, Gillian, circa 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Jarden, Richards, circa 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Jean Freeman Gallery, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Jeff, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Jemison, Noah, circa 1983-circa 1993 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Jerome Foundation Fellowship Program, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Jochimsen, Margarethe, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - John Gibson Commissions, Inc., circa 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Johnson, Elaine, 1967-1979 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Johnson, Ellen, 1972-1983 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Johnson, Martha, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Johnson, Patricia, 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Johnson, Poppy, circa 1970s (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Johnson, Ray, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Johnson, Ray, 1946-1968 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Johnson, Ray, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Johnson, Ray, 1971-1982 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Johnson, Ray, New York Corres-Sponge-Dance School of Vancouver, circa 1968-1974 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      Includes 2 issues of File; oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 3
    - Jones, Diane Allen, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Judd, Donald, 1994; circa 1956-1976 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Junior League of Chicago, Inc., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Just Above Midtown, Inc., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - J, General: Ja, 1960s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - J, General: Je, 1970s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - J, General: Ji-Joh, 1970s-2000 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - J, General: Jon-Ju, 1960s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - J, First Names Only: Ja-Ji, 1970s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - J, First Names Only: Jo-Ju, 1960s-1992 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Kahn, Douglas, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Kahrl, Marguerite B., 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Kalkmann, Hans-Werner, 1960s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Kalmia, circa 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Kaltenbach, Stephen, circa 1968-circa 1972 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Kaprow, Allan, 1967-1980s (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Karlin, Renata, circa 1972-circa 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Karras, Maria, circa 1974-1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Katz, Leandro, 1970s-1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Katzen, Lila, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kawara, On, circa 1969-1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Kazis, Jill, 1980s (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Kelly, Mary, 1970s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Kenedy, Robert C., circa 1968-1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Kennedy, Peter and Barbara, circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Kennedy, Peter and Barbara, 1974-circa 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Kiddle, Catherine and Peter, circa 1970s-circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Kiddle, Catherine and Peter, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Kiddle, Catherine and Peter, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Kiddle, Catherine and Peter, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Kindness, John, 1980s-1990s (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Kinmont, Bob, circa 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 3 and OV 58
    - Kirby, Michael, 1960s-1970s (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Includes photo of Kirby
    - Kirili, Alan, circa 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Kitchel, Nancy Wilson, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Korell, Karen S. (The Accumulation), 1970s (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Kornblum, Helen, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)